<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/</id>
    <title>Log on!</title>
    <updated>2020-01-17T07:26:32.160Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>Fieldnotes by Joy</subtitle>
    <logo>https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, Log on!</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday, Jan 17 2020// I lost HKD$0.5]]></title>
        <id>https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/post/friday-jan-17-2020-i-lost-hkddollar05</id>
        <link href="https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/post/friday-jan-17-2020-i-lost-hkddollar05">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-01-17T07:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today's shift: 11:45-14:45</p>
<p>The second order was by a male mainland student and he lives in a 唐樓. Somehow, we two chinese mainlander are speaking English to each other....and I was focusing on his cat, wondering at the door when he was trying to pull out his money....after he shut the door I realized there is 0.5 dollar less! However, I felt embarassed to go back and asked for the money... I tried to reach CS but CS said either I paid or I went back and asked for the money.. I was like speachless. Gel told me that's the case.</p>
<p>Third order, I spent almost 10 mins looking for the customer's building. End up that is a fancy resident place in No. 1, Sai Yuen Ln........</p>
<p>The customer is nice in the phone but when I went up, he opens the door while hiding behind the door and only reached out his hand to me.... I pondered a little bit and he murmured a littble bit as well, indicating me to pass on the bag.</p>
<p>Gel told me about his past experience as a walker working around Central, Western Island area and how he suffered from the height in this area. He also told me the disavantages being a fake contract employer as the system would send him the orders with longest distances which passed on by other riders...</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday Jan 16, 2019// A Walker came by and talked to me...]]></title>
        <id>https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/post/jan-16-2019-friday</id>
        <link href="https://jiuchiroulin88.github.io/foodpanda.github.io/post/jan-16-2019-friday">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-01-16T19:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Shift: 13:45-15:45</p>
<p>A middle-aged man stopped in front of me and initiated a conversation by asking how is the frequency of orders today.😁</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>